123orkut.com 2012-09-02

# 123orkut.com - Orkut Scraps | Orkut Images | Orkut Mp3 | Orkut Graphics

At 123orkut.com, we understand that independent journalists and whistle blowers are often subject to harassment or threats to their safety. We also understand that average, everyday citizens may not want their personal information spread across the web, especially in the face of large data mining operations where a users identity is sold to advertisers.

In order to create a safe space for people to be the media, we are very careful to not store your personal information, only doing so when you have explicitly given it to us or given us permission to do so. 

1\. We do not log IP addresses, user agents, or other personally identifiable information. We store your username, email address, and any other information provided during registration however we only store that information which you have explicitly given us.

2\. If the site encounters an error then information on who caused that error may be stored to our logs including the username, IP address, user agent, time, and what the user was trying to do. We log these in case people try and break the security on our site. These logs should not be generated in normal course of utilizing the site.

3\. If you send us a support request or something of that matter, we will store copies of those requests until the problem is resolved. This includes any information you sent us in those requests. When your request has been resolved, you will receive a notification email that your request has been deleted. If you do not, please follow up and make sure that the privacy policy is enforced.

4\. Occasionally, we may need to look at server logs or generate them in order to diagnose problems with the site. These logs may contain any information that you or your browser knowingly or unknowingly submits to us, including your IP address. In such cases, the logs will be deleted when they are no longer needed and the problem has been resolved.

5\. Any updates made to this policy will be published to the main page of the site and posted to the “all” list.

* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here. 

Unfortunately, we at 123orkut.com might not be able to protect your anonymity and privacy from all avenues of attack. Your connections are logged by your place of work, school, internet service provider, and various government agencies. Furthermore, our servers are not protected by armed guards or state of the art firewalls, so our server settings could theoretically be modified by an adversary. If this is of concern to you, you need to take charge and use a program such as [Tor](http://www.torproject.org/) to protect your identity.
